<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<ystfeed>
<vespaadd><document type="wisdom">
<uri>432470</uri>
<subject>Why are yawns contagious?</subject>
<content>When people yawn, you see that other people in the room yawn, too.  Why is that?</content>
<bestanswer>When your body need more oxygen, you yawn.  &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;When you yawn, you take more oxygen in the air.  &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;If the density of the oxygen in the air becomes lower, other people (their bodies) can feel that and start to yawn to get more oxygen.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;That's why yawns are contagious. Yawning is extremely contagious -- 55% of people who witness someone yawn will yawn within five minutes. If a visually impaired person hears a tape of someone yawning, he or she is likely to yawn as well. Face it, the likelihood of you making it to the end of this answer without looking like one of these gaping maws is unlikely. &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Although the contagious nature of yawning is well established, we know less about why this is so. Researchers are currently giving the topic some serious attention. One theory suggests it's a holdover from a period in evolutionary history when yawning served to coordinate the social behavior of a group of animals. A recent study postulates that contagious yawning could be part of the "neural network involved in empathy." &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;While the mystery of contagious yawning has yet to be solved, perhaps researchers are closing in on an answer. On the other hand, given the subject matter, we wouldn't blame them for falling asleep at the wheel. In the meantime, give the "yawn challenge" a try -- it's tougher than it looks.</bestanswer>
<nbestanswers><answer_item>Yawning is extremely contagious -- 55% of people who witness someone yawn will yawn within five minutes. If a visually impaired person hears a tape of someone yawning, he or she is likely to yawn as well. Face it, the likelihood of you making it to the end of this answer without looking like one of these gaping maws is unlikely. &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Although the contagious nature of yawning is well established, we know less about why this is so. Researchers are currently giving the topic some serious attention. One theory suggests it's a holdover from a period in evolutionary history when yawning served to coordinate the social behavior of a group of animals. A recent study postulates that contagious yawning could be part of the "neural network involved in empathy." &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;While the mystery of contagious yawning has yet to be solved, perhaps researchers are closing in on an answer. On the other hand, given the subject matter, we wouldn't blame them for falling asleep at the wheel. In the meantime, give the "yawn challenge" a try -- it's tougher than it looks.</answer_item>
<answer_item>When your body need more oxygen, you yawn.  &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;When you yawn, you take more oxygen in the air.  &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;If the density of the oxygen in the air becomes lower, other people (their bodies) can feel that and start to yawn to get more oxygen.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;That's why yawns are contagious.</answer_item>
</nbestanswers>
<cat>Trivia</cat>
<maincat>Education &amp; Reference</maincat>
<subcat>Trivia</subcat>
<date>1127631600</date>
<res_date>1120237002</res_date>
<vot_date>1127977920</vot_date>
<lastanswerts>1161068399</lastanswerts>
<qlang>en</qlang>
<qintl>us</qintl>
<language>en-us</language>
<id>u1254780</id>
<best_id>u1305446</best_id>
</document></vespaadd>
<vespaadd><document type="wisdom">
<uri>800062</uri>
<subject>What's the best way to heat up a cold hamburger (In &amp; Out)?</subject>
<content>What's the best way to heat up a cold hamburger (In &amp; Out)?</content>
<bestanswer>If you must eat a heated In &amp; Out hamburger then I suggest the follow:&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;First, scrape the ketchup, mayo and any other sauce that is on the hamburger and put it a side. Also take the vegetables out.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Second, pre-heat a steak pan; put the hamburger separate form the bun on the hot pan&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Third, heat up both parts of the bun near the hamburger on the same hot pan (you can get some souce from the hamburger on it)&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Fourth, you can either put back the original ketchup, mayo and the vegetables or, better yet, get new ones from what you have at home .&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Bon Appetite</bestanswer>
<nbestanswers><answer_item>If you must eat a heated In &amp; Out hamburger then I suggest the follow:&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;First, scrape the ketchup, mayo and any other sauce that is on the hamburger and put it a side. Also take the vegetables out.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Second, pre-heat a steak pan; put the hamburger separate form the bun on the hot pan&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Third, heat up both parts of the bun near the hamburger on the same hot pan (you can get some souce from the hamburger on it)&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Fourth, you can either put back the original ketchup, mayo and the vegetables or, better yet, get new ones from what you have at home .&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Bon Appetite</answer_item>
<answer_item>probably a microwave. in norway for example, outside of the main cities, because it's so remote, they have frozen hamburgers in roadside joints, and heat them up per request. &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;as with all microwave heating, it will be a bit soggy...</answer_item>
</nbestanswers>
<cat>Cooking &amp; Recipes</cat>
<maincat>Food &amp; Drink</maincat>
<subcat>Cooking &amp; Recipes</subcat>
<date>1122361200</date>
<res_date>1123511997</res_date>
<lastanswerts>1161068399</lastanswerts>
<qlang>en</qlang>
<qintl>us</qintl>
<language>en-us</language>
<id>u1305446</id>
<best_id>u484353</best_id>
</document></vespaadd>
<vespaadd><document type="wisdom">
<uri>1532796</uri>
<subject>Vacation rentals in the Turks and Caicos</subject>
<content>We are considering renting a house in the Turks and Caicos... any recommendations of which islands might be best, and good places to rent from?</content>
<bestanswer>I like Providenciales best. Beautiful beaches are scattered on all sides of Providenciales, the most spectacular of which is a 12 mile stretch located on Grace Bay, which is protected by a healthy barrier reef. Provo has an 18 hole golf course, a casino, shopping centres, three marinas, a growing number of of bars and excellent restaurants. Provo is also a divers' and water lovers' paradise.</bestanswer>
<nbestanswers><answer_item>I like Providenciales best. Beautiful beaches are scattered on all sides of Providenciales, the most spectacular of which is a 12 mile stretch located on Grace Bay, which is protected by a healthy barrier reef. Provo has an 18 hole golf course, a casino, shopping centres, three marinas, a growing number of of bars and excellent restaurants. Provo is also a divers' and water lovers' paradise.</answer_item>
</nbestanswers>
<cat>Turks &amp; Caicos</cat>
<maincat>Travel</maincat>
<subcat>Caribbean</subcat>
<date>1120722045</date>
<res_date>1121234441</res_date>
<lastanswerts>1161068399</lastanswerts>
<qlang>en</qlang>
<qintl>us</qintl>
<language>en-us</language>
<id>u455489</id>
<best_id>u1558834</best_id>
</document></vespaadd>
<vespaadd><document type="wisdom">
<uri>50082</uri>
<subject>what has more caffeine? a double latte or a large coffee?</subject>
<content>choosing between a double latte (or similar) and a 16oz cup of drip coffee, which would have more caffeine?</content>
<bestanswer>Based on this&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;http://coffeefaq.com/caffaq.html&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;I would say that a large coffe has about 80-135mg of caffeine, but a double latte (which has 2 espresso shots) has about 200mg+</bestanswer>
<nbestanswers><answer_item>Based on this&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;http://coffeefaq.com/caffaq.html&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;I would say that a large coffe has about 80-135mg of caffeine, but a double latte (which has 2 espresso shots) has about 200mg+</answer_item>
<answer_item>Depends on what type of coffee. Typically espresso uses darker roasted blends which actually have less caffeine. FOr example and Italian roast has less caffeine than french roast. It also depends on how strong the coffee is. Here is some more interesting info which will guide you against latte's&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;http://www.cockeyed.com/inside/coffee/coffee.html&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;And finally, if you order some complex bullshit like a double-tall, half-caff, skim Mochachino with light foam &amp; two ice-cubes, you are 50% more likely to have someone spit in your drink.</answer_item>
</nbestanswers>
<cat>Non-Alcoholic Drinks</cat>
<maincat>Food &amp; Drink</maincat>
<subcat>Non-Alcoholic Drinks</subcat>
<date>1120843369</date>
<res_date>1120862919</res_date>
<lastanswerts>1161068399</lastanswerts>
<qlang>en</qlang>
<qintl>us</qintl>
<language>en-us</language>
<id>u758956</id>
<best_id>u505916</best_id>
</document></vespaadd>
<vespaadd><document type="wisdom">
<uri>2318984</uri>
<subject>what convertible has five seats</subject>
<content>looking for something that can seat three kids, with seatbelts etc.</content>
<bestanswer>My 1973 convertable Cadilac El Camino had no problem holding 6 full-sized adults. [See the picture.]&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;It's a bit of a gas guzzler, though...</bestanswer>
<nbestanswers><answer_item>My 1973 convertable Cadilac El Camino had no problem holding 6 full-sized adults. [See the picture.]&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;It's a bit of a gas guzzler, though...</answer_item>
</nbestanswers>
<cat>Other - Cars &amp; Transportation</cat>
<maincat>Cars &amp; Transportation</maincat>
<subcat>Other - Cars &amp; Transportation</subcat>
<date>1122429380</date>
<res_date>1124156853</res_date>
<lastanswerts>1161068399</lastanswerts>
<qlang>en</qlang>
<qintl>us</qintl>
<language>en-us</language>
<id>u758956</id>
<best_id>u1827235</best_id>
</document></vespaadd>
<vespaadd><document type="wisdom">
<uri>3178830</uri>
<subject>why doesn't an optical mouse work on a glass table?</subject>
<content>or even on some surfaces?</content>
<bestanswer>Optical mice use an LED and a camera to rapidly capture images of the surface beneath the mouse.  The infomation from the camera is analyzed by a DSP (Digital Signal Processor) and used to detect imperfections in the underlying surface and determine motion. Some materials, such as glass, mirrors or other very shiny, uniform surfaces interfere with the ability of the DSP to accurately analyze the surface beneath the mouse.  &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Since glass is transparent and very uniform, the mouse is unable to pick up enough imperfections in the underlying surface to determine motion.  Mirrored surfaces are also a problem, since they constantly reflect back the same image, causing the DSP not to recognize motion properly. When the system is unable to see surface changes associated with movement, the mouse will not work properly.</bestanswer>
<nbestanswers><answer_item>Optical mice use an LED and a camera to rapidly capture images of the surface beneath the mouse.  The infomation from the camera is analyzed by a DSP (Digital Signal Processor) and used to detect imperfections in the underlying surface and determine motion. Some materials, such as glass, mirrors or other very shiny, uniform surfaces interfere with the ability of the DSP to accurately analyze the surface beneath the mouse.  &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Since glass is transparent and very uniform, the mouse is unable to pick up enough imperfections in the underlying surface to determine motion.  Mirrored surfaces are also a problem, since they constantly reflect back the same image, causing the DSP not to recognize motion properly. When the system is unable to see surface changes associated with movement, the mouse will not work properly.</answer_item>
</nbestanswers>
<cat>Add-ons</cat>
<maincat>Computers &amp; Internet</maincat>
<subcat>Hardware</subcat>
<date>1122587045</date>
<res_date>1122939281</res_date>
<lastanswerts>1161068399</lastanswerts>
<qlang>en</qlang>
<qintl>us</qintl>
<language>en-us</language>
<id>u758956</id>
<best_id>u228028</best_id>
</document></vespaadd>
<vespaadd><document type="wisdom">
<uri>2020338</uri>
<subject>Why did the U.S Invade Iraq ?</subject>
<content>Why did the U.S Invade Iraq ?</content>
<bestanswer>A small group of politicians believed strongly that the fact that Saddam Hussien remained in power after the first Gulf War was a signal of weakness to the rest of the world, one that invited attacks and terrorism. Shortly after taking power with George Bush in 2000 and after the attack on 9/11, they were able to use the terrorist attacks to justify war with Iraq on this basis and exaggerated threats of the development of weapons of mass destruction. The military strength of the U.S. and the brutality of Saddam's regime led them to imagine that the military and political victory would be relatively easy.</bestanswer>
<nbestanswers><answer_item>A small group of politicians believed strongly that the fact that Saddam Hussien remained in power after the first Gulf War was a signal of weakness to the rest of the world, one that invited attacks and terrorism. Shortly after taking power with George Bush in 2000 and after the attack on 9/11, they were able to use the terrorist attacks to justify war with Iraq on this basis and exaggerated threats of the development of weapons of mass destruction. The military strength of the U.S. and the brutality of Saddam's regime led them to imagine that the military and political victory would be relatively easy.</answer_item>
<answer_item>Because there is a lot of oil in Iraq.</answer_item>
<answer_item>It is tempting to say that the US invaded Iraq because it has lots of oil, but the US is not a country in a deep economic problem that capturing other country’s oil is an actual need for survival. It is more likely that the Iraq invading Kuwait scenario would fall under that assumption.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;I think that the US government has come to a conclusion that we are on the verge of a war of religions, or more likely ideologies. It would be presumptuous to try and determent a one cause to the coming war. &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;I think that the world wide spread of the media with its many forms (Cable, Satellite, Internet, etc.)  have pushed the Moslem regimes to the extreme, fearing that secularity and democratic influence is penetrating their country and will result in an up raising against them. One of the best way to maintain the power that you have and even gain more of it, is by hatred. When the common man is occupied hating an outside enemy, its hatred is kept out side the county and would not be directed towards the regime. &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;So- I believe that the US understands that the fanatic Moslem regimes have already started a war on the democratic world and now is the time to try a fight it.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;So why invade Iraq? Because it is a huge, week Moslem country that thought to be easy to defeat. &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;This is exactly the same reason why Afghanistan was first and Syria is next in line.</answer_item>
<answer_item>I think Yuval is pretty spot on. It's a proving ground and a focal point for terror activity that's not on American soil. And, because no one liked Saddam Hussein, no other countries (even in the Middle East) were about to rise up and join his side.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;Rabid speculation: now the Pentagon has a model that says it takes ~5 years, ~$200B and ~2,000 casualties to "rebuild" a dictatorship into a democracy. Who's next on the list?</answer_item>
</nbestanswers>
<cat>Current Events</cat>
<maincat>News &amp; Events</maincat>
<subcat>Current Events</subcat>
<date>1127199600</date>
<res_date>1129940520</res_date>
<vot_date>1127856720</vot_date>
<lastanswerts>1161068399</lastanswerts>
<qlang>en</qlang>
<qintl>us</qintl>
<language>en-us</language>
<id>u785001</id>
<best_id>u1372188</best_id>
</document></vespaadd>
<vespaadd><document type="wisdom">
<uri>2534366</uri>
<subject>best finish for concrete surfaces</subject>
<content>best finish for concrete surfaces</content>
<bestanswer>it depends what you're looking for, and what tolerance you have for cost.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;simple plain finish (and similarly broom finish which is basically going over the wet concrete with a broom to make patterns) are very cheap but also have a basic look (cheap look).&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;high end finish is imprinted concrete, which can make it look like natual stone or bricks - very flexible. this tends to be MUCH more expensive. &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;another thing to consider is that concrete surfaces tend to crack, and this shows at different levels in different finishes. impronted and plain finish tends to show the cracks very prominently. other finishes like exposed aggregate (small pebbles on top of the concrete that are exposed and showing on top) tend to have cracks be less visible.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;i attached an example of one company that provides different finishes. from my experience they are way overpriced so you want to shop around.</bestanswer>
<nbestanswers><answer_item>it depends what you're looking for, and what tolerance you have for cost.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;simple plain finish (and similarly broom finish which is basically going over the wet concrete with a broom to make patterns) are very cheap but also have a basic look (cheap look).&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;high end finish is imprinted concrete, which can make it look like natual stone or bricks - very flexible. this tends to be MUCH more expensive. &lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;another thing to consider is that concrete surfaces tend to crack, and this shows at different levels in different finishes. impronted and plain finish tends to show the cracks very prominently. other finishes like exposed aggregate (small pebbles on top of the concrete that are exposed and showing on top) tend to have cracks be less visible.&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;i attached an example of one company that provides different finishes. from my experience they are way overpriced so you want to shop around.</answer_item>
</nbestanswers>
<cat>Maintenance &amp; Repairs</cat>
<maincat>Home &amp; Garden</maincat>
<subcat>Maintenance &amp; Repairs</subcat>
<date>1122534000</date>
<res_date>1122915817</res_date>
<lastanswerts>1161068399</lastanswerts>
<qlang>en</qlang>
<qintl>us</qintl>
<language>en-us</language>
<id>u435622</id>
<best_id>u758956</best_id>
</document></vespaadd>
<vespaadd><document type="wisdom">
<uri>3416927</uri>
<subject>What is the best off-road motorcycle trail ?</subject>
<content>long-distance trail throughout CA</content>
<bestanswer>i hear that the mojave road is amazing!&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;search for it online.</bestanswer>
<nbestanswers><answer_item>i hear that the mojave road is amazing!&lt;br /&gt;&#xa;search for it online.</answer_item>
<answer_item>Tzeelim army base. Some podra but you can handle it.</answer_item>
</nbestanswers>
<cat>Hunting</cat>
<maincat>Sports</maincat>
<subcat>Outdoor Recreation</subcat>
<date>1127631600</date>
<res_date>1129854120</res_date>
<vot_date>1127977320</vot_date>
<lastanswerts>1161068399</lastanswerts>
<qlang>en</qlang>
<qintl>us</qintl>
<language>en-us</language>
<id>u1401694</id>
</document></vespaadd>
</ystfeed>
